

# Chacha Zhou(周伟) □

Crypto.com - Foris Technology (Shenzhen) Limited / Senior Software Engineer

7 Years Experience / College Degree / 29 Years Old

☐ 13798247501 ☐ chachazw@gmail.com

### Profile

Execution Team spirit Self-driven Adaptability English

Over 7 years full-stack experience, and developed many projects during this time, including React and Vue web app, Web3 dapp, React-Native app, WeChat mini-program, Flutter hybrid app, and also have some Nodejs experience, and as a team leader of 10 members before.

## Work Experience



Crypto.com - Foris Technology (Shenzhen) Limited. / Exchange Team

2022.05-Currently

Senior Software Engineer

React Vue3 CI/CD Typescript

- 1. As a senior software engineer in a large front-end team, responsible for the crypto.com Exchange core features development, including security dashboard, affiliate dashboard, ect.
- 2. Integrate Yubikey web authn to Exchange security dashboard with backend developers, and add Yubikey bridges for Android and iOS platform, improve web and app security.
- 3. Integrate components to UI component library X-UI, and develop UI developer tools to facilitate development and debugging, add Jest unit jest to UI components and improve test coverage.
- 4. Responsible for CI/CD for our Exchange and Yubikey project, integrate Circle CI and Github actions to our Exchange Vue3 migration project.
- 5. Responsible for technology architecture of Vue3 migration project, bring monorepo best practise and develop playground developer tools for Exchange Vue3 migration project and improve page development efficiency.



Candela (Shenzhen) Technology Innovation Co. Ltd. / R&D department

2019.01-2022.04

Front-end Team Leader

( React ) ( Vue ) ( Gatsby ) ( Flutter ) ( Dart ) ( Typescript )

- 1. As the leader of the large front-end technical team, responsible for the project management and R&D of the web, mobile HTML5, mini-program and Flutter App, responsible for the mobile cross-platform technology R&D and project management, engineering and automatic deployment, technology selection and technology challenge.
- 2. Team management, task arrangement and scheduling, follow up front-end project development progress, improve frontend workflow and product experience, participate in product requirements, interaction and design discussions, and formulate suitable solutions.

- 3. Team building, regularly hold technical sharing within the team, create a cultural atmosphere of engineers, regular team technical training, improve team technical level and R&D ability.
- 4. Responsible for visual monitoring of front-end large-screen robots, video monitoring and remote control of robots, as well as architecture design and technology research and development of visual graphics editing tools, and develop visual applications using D3, fabricJS, ThreeJS, and other frameworks.
- 5. Responsible for the cross-platform technology architecture design of native iOS and Android apps and Flutter, combined with native technology and Flutter cross-platform technology hybrid development, to solve the problem of multiple-end reuse of a set of codes.



#### Plum Flower International LLC / R&D department

2017.06-2019.01

Front-end Team Leader





- 1. Served as the technical leader of a 7-person front-end development team from all over the world, responsible for frontend project technology research and development, front-end performance optimization, front-end architecture design and technology selection, front-end engineering and automatic deployment of large-scale US municipal projects.
- 2. Team management, task arrangement and scheduling, follow up front-end project development progress, improve frontend workflow and product experience, participate in product requirements, interaction and design discussions, and formulate suitable solutions.



#### For Change LLC / R&D department

2016.08-2017.06

Front-end Developer





(Vue) (VueX) (Node.js) (Javascript)

- 1. As a core member of the technical team, responsible for the front-end development technology selection, technical architecture, the front-end page refactoring, and implementation of interactive logic and create some amazing animations, data processing of the front-end, and develop progressive front-end page.
- 2. Use the Express node back-end framework as the middle layer to develop the front-end data interface, use Vue front-end framework to develop the book management system SPA, use Vuex as the data state management tool, use Gulp and Webpack to package and compress project files, and front-end development CI/CD.
- 3. Responsible for the front-end development of millions of user-level products, formulate product release processes and code specifications, and design WeChat WebApp multi-page project architecture and workflow.



# Ai Ying Internet Culture Co., Ltd. / R&D department

2015.07-2016.08

Front-end Developer



Responsible for the front-end development technology selection architecture design, the front-end page refactoring, and implementation of interactive logic. Use React + Redux + Ant Design + NodeJS + Webpack to build video editor platform.

# **Project Experience**

Crypto.com Exchange

2022.5-Currently

Crypto.com Exchange is a large cryptocurrency exchange that is developed with Vue2 and Vue3 frameworks, and with over 70 million users worldwide.

- 1. Develop front-end features with Vue2 and Vue3 frameworks.
- 2. Integrate Circle CI and Github Actions to CI/CD workflow.
- 3. Responsible for handling browser compatibility issues and improve the stability of website.
- 4. Responsible for handling browser compatibility issues and improve the stability of website.

#### Post Warehouse Management Flutter App

2020.08-2021.10

Post Warehouse Management is a cross-platform mobile enterprise business management application developed with Flutter. The main core businesses include device management, smart packing, scanning code pickup, takeaway order management, shared order management, stranded items management, etc. It is a robotic intelligent business management application.

- 1. Build the basic technical architecture of Flutter and develop the core business logic.
- 2. Developed Flutter component modules cti\_services, cti\_widgets, cti\_utils and other common component modules.
- 3. Introducing Redux state management mechanism to Flutter applications.
- 4. Responsible for handling Android and iOS cross-platform compatibility issues.

### Large Scale Business Management Platform

2019.02-2020.10

The business management platform is a large-scale background management system for the robot industry, which integrates express delivery business, takeaway delivery business, and robot shared delivery business. It also includes device management and control platform, robot real-time monitoring system. Monitoring center, reconciliation management, user management, message center and other core business modules.

- 1. Use React and Typescript stack to build the basic technical architecture of the background management system from scratch, create front-end development, public component library development, unit testing and Git workflow specifications.
- 2. Responsible for the technology research and development of related core modules of the business management platform, including large-screen data monitoring, real-time robot monitoring, authority management, and use D3 to build robot device visualization.

**Aurora Company App** 2018.05-2019.01

Aurora Company App is an enterprise recruitment service SaaS application that integrates job posting, personnel recruitment and instant communication. Enterprises can publish recruitment information on this platform and communicate with candidates online. There is an Aurora Candidate App on the client side. Ordinary users can find suitable job opportunities on this platform, and at the same time, they can communicate with enterprises online, voice and video, and share files online.

- 1. As the front-end development leader, lead 6 developers from all over the world to develop collaboratively remotely, formulate detailed development tasks, reasonably assign tasks to team members, and ensure efficient team collaboration.
- 2. Design the front-end infrastructure and front-end development workflow, formulate a unified front-end modular development standard, and provide a stable architectural foundation for the team to write high-quality code.

- 3. Unify front-end code specifications, write front-end code specification documents, standardize front-end code styles, and establish code style Check Lists, providing team members with a good coding foundation.
- 4. Formulated the Git standardized workflow and front-end code review process, and worked with Devops developers to formulate the automatic deployment process of web applications to ensure the continuous integration and continuous delivery.
- 5. Formulate the development specifications and standards of the front-end UI component library, use Storybook to collaboratively develop common component libraries and component description documents, use Rollup to package and compress and publish the UI component library on NPM, providing for the development of web applications the possibility of multiplexing and expansion solves the coupling problem between multiple applications.
- 6. Formulate the front-end component Jest test specification, and worked with team members to write component test cases, which improved the front-end component test coverage and reduced the code error rate.

#### Eco Web App (Plum Flower International LLC)

2017.06-2018.09

EcoAppPro is the new standard for urban utility management software and is an efficient and modern mobile GIS integration system. The project is a responsive large-scale integrated front-end project developed using the react technology stack, including Communications, User Center, Assets, System Manager, Personnel, and Logbook.

- 1. As the head of front-end technology, design and build the front-end technology infrastructure, lead 5 front-end members to develop collaboratively, and formulate reasonable development tasks.
- 2. Write relatively common front-end development standards, assign tasks to team members on Jira, review member codes, and control the progress of front-end development to achieve agile project development.
- 3. The technology stacks used in the project include React, Redux, React-router, Recompose, Redux-saga, Flow and Semantic-ui-react, etc., and use the above technology stacks to build a stable and efficient front-end technology architecture, design and develop reusable front-end foundations components.
- 4. Develop Fetch-based HTTP asynchronous request service, load server-side data asynchronously, process and cache complex data, and solve CORS cross-domain requests.
- 5. Use webpack to achieve a series of engineering development, including compression and packaging of front-end resource files, generation and merging of front-end CSS style files, front-end JS code segmentation and asynchronous loading, and use CDN caching services to improve the performance and experience of the web app.
- 6. Use Jest testing tool to build a front-end testing environment and write complete unit test cases for React components to improve components quality and test coverage.

## **Education**

Shenzhen University 2021-Currently

Bachelor Degree / Computer Science and Applications

Shenzhen Polytechnic 2013-2016

College Degree / Communication Technology

English CET-6 / Fluent